Guide to the Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County records, 1914-2010
Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County records, 1914-2010
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County records, 1914-2010.
4287
Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County.
8 cubic ft.
Reports, programs, meeting minutes, photographs, newsclippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
General files related to county extension work, including publications, reports, photographs, and meeting minutes
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
General files related to county extension work.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County.
Subjects:
Agricultural extension work.; Home economics extension work.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Annual Home Bureau Report and Agents Reports, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Home Bureau Report and Agents Reports, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Report of County Extension Workers, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Semi-Annual Report - Home Bureau, 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Semi-Annual Report - Home Bureau, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Semi-Annual Report - Home Bureau, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Annual Report - Home Demonstration Work, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dryden Home Demonstration Unit, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Records and History of East Lawn, 1925-1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Home Bureau Creed (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reorganization of Home Economics Extension Program from Home Bureau, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Formation of Tompkins County Food Conservation - History and Minutes, 1917-1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ledger Book - Home Bureau Executive Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Home Bureau Executive Committee, 1924-1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Home Bureau Executive Committee, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Home Bureau Executive Committee - Annual Meeting Minutes (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Home Economics Newsclippings, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Nomination for Home Economics Program Committee, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Pictures and Negatives, 1920-1930's (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
- Financial Statements, 1923-1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Scrapbook - Picture of upholstered chairs, 1920's (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Information and bulletins related to kitchens, 1938-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Forecast magazine - article by Marguerite Dixon, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Scrapbook - Newspaper clippings, 1917-1921 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Dimension, published by The Cooperative Extension Association of Tompkins County, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Dimension, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Dimension, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Dimension, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Dimension, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Dimension, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Dimension, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Dimension, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Dimension, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Dimension, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Dimension, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dimension, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Dimension, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Dimension, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dimension, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Dimension, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Dimension, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Dimension, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Dimension, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Family Focus: Home Economics Newsletter, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1922, Revised, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Association History (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Association History Organization Reports, 1959-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Association History Organization Reports, 1970-1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Association History Organization Reports, 1924-1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Memorandum of Agreements, 1929-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- World Policy Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Membership Campaigns, lists and committeemen, 1914-1956 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- DHIA and Dairy Council and Farm Council (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Other Organizations: SCS, ACP, Land Use Commission, Home Marketing Association, 1930- (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Other Organizations: Agricultural Security Commission, Resettlement Administration, War Board, Mobilization, 1935-1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Other Organizations: Agricultural Pioneer Artificial Breeding Cooperative (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Agricultural Soil Survey Maps (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Budgets and Payrolls, 1924-1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- CRD Program Committee, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Program Committee Minutes, pre 1955 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Program Committee Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Program Committee Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Program Committee Minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Program Committee Minutes, 1969-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Home Economics Committee Members, Agents, Member Information, 1935-1955 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Agricultural "Drive It Yourself Tour", 1961-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Program and Plan of Work, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Agricultural Program and Plan of Work, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Agricultural Program and Plan of Work, 1942-1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Agriculture Quarterly and Monthly Reports, 1952-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agriculture Annual Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agriculture News Articles, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Junior Extension and 4-H Memorandums and Reports, 1923-1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 4-H Radio Scripts, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 4-H Monthly and Quarterly Report, 1957-1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 4-H Monthly and Quarterly Report, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association Annual Meetings, 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Association Annual Meetings, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Cooperative Extension Annual Reports, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Tompkins County Extension Service Board Minutes and Records, 1929-1955 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- History of 4-H, 1932-1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Board of Directors and Committees, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1916-1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Family and Community Development
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Information, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Information, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Information, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Parent Education Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Program Evaluation, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Class Evaluations - Trumansburg, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series - Materials, 1989-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Facilitator Training Evaluations, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Information, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Program Evaluations and Materials, 1983-1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Facilitator Training Evaluations, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series- Materials, Budgets and Reports, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Facilitator Manual Project, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Advisory Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series CARDI Evaluation Project, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Parenting - Materials, Budgets and Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Materials and Facilitator Training, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Parenting - Focus Group Summary, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Parenting Evaluation of Parenting Skills Workshop Series, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Parenting - Child Abuse Prevention Conference, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Parent Support Group, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Evaluations and Facilitator Manuals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series General Materials and Facilitator Training, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Parenting - CARDI Programs, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Interview Transcripts, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Materials, Final Report and Family Resolution Project, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Evaluation, Annual Report, and Facilitator Training, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Parenting - Graduate Student Research, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Annual Reports and Budgets, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Pilot Programs, 1994-1995; 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Facilitated Visits, Education Training, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Parent Feedback, 2004, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Evaluation Data, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Materials, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Parenting the Hardest Job in the World, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Parenting the Hardest Job in the World - Program and Evaluation, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Summary, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Parenting Skills Workshop Series Tioga County Data, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Focus Groups, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - General Notes, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - General Notes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - General Notes, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Legal Issues/P.E.A.C.E., 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Trainee Manual Drafts, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Resource Materials, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Advisory Group, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Curriculum Manual, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Evaluation, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Statewide Dissemination Training Workshops, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Handouts, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Funding-State Program Committee and REIGP Grants, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Funding-Miscellaneous Grants, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Funding Applied for, Not Received, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Program Development - Legislation, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Community Dispute Resolution Center Coordination - Advisory Group, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Community Dispute Resolution Center Coordination - Funding, 2003-2006 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Community Dispute Resolution Center Coordination - Early Curriculum, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Community Dispute Resolution Center Coordination - Statewide, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Cornell Cooperative Extension-Tompkins County -, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Cornell Cooperative Extension-Tompkins County -, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Cornell Cooperative Extension-Tompkins County -, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Parenting; Parents Apart, Cornell Cooperative Extension-Tompkins County - Facilitator's Manual, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Timeline Summary, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Project Proposal, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Project Proposal and Contract, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Advisory Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Outreach - Public Service Announcements, 2000-2006 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Video Project, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Correspondence with Judi Smith, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Procedural Manual, Pilot Program, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Materials for Participants, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Team Meetings Notes, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, PSWS Evaluation with Parents Count, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Funding, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, VAWA-Safe Havens, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Pilot Project Evaluation, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Funding Proposal to OCFS, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, Funding Proposal to TCGF, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Parenting; Parents Count, F and CS All-Ways Parenting Proposal, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Effective Black Parenting Program, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Parenting; Culturally Sensitive Parenting, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Parenting; Culturally Sensitive Parenting, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Effective Black Parenting Program, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Parenting; Discipline Workshops, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Parenting; Clover-opoly Program, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Parenting; Programs on Violence, Resource Materials and Parent Education Manual, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Parenting; "Not in My School, Not in My Community" Program, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)